<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Achievements on Matteo Minutti</title>
    <link>https://minutti.it/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Achievements on Matteo Minutti</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://minutti.it/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Indie Project</title>
      <link>https://minutti.it/projects/first-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minutti.it/projects/first-project/</guid>
      <description>When I was 19, me and some friend started a collective business aiming to blow up in the hiphop music scene.
No, I&amp;rsquo;m not a rapper or something like that, I&amp;rsquo;ve just only had a good idea to manage all our single talents in a single funnel.
This funnel is Sao Square Corp., our collective name.
We&amp;rsquo;re just skilled guys with different scopes, and we&amp;rsquo;re tryna to make something big all together; I&amp;rsquo;ve done some job of administration and started my first business as freelance developer, managing alone the website construction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Paid Job</title>
      <link>https://minutti.it/projects/first-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minutti.it/projects/first-job/</guid>
      <description>At the age of 21, during my third year at computer engineering and a bit of late exams, I was feeling a little tired of financial status and a little afraid of afraid of burdening my family; Confident in the knowledge that I had managed successfully a website development pipeline (without having any idea what I was doing), Thought I&amp;rsquo;d comparing myself with an enterprise environment in order to understand all mistakes I made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Business</title>
      <link>https://minutti.it/projects/first-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minutti.it/projects/first-business/</guid>
      <description>After a somewhat eventful period, I&amp;rsquo;ve met Mr. Fiorilli that believing in my capabilities at the age of 23 proposes me to co-found a company, in which I would have had the total responsibility for software developments.
Thus began, on July 18 2019, my adventure as CEO (and also CTO) in SILPH Technologies. In these two years we developed few product and service and many PoC, hired a developer and conquer some important customers onto international panorama, e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
